const quiz = {
  0: [
    {
      question: 'What is the standard abbreviation for your Charisma score?',
      correctAnswer: 'CHA',
      answers: [
        'CHA',
        'DEX',
        'WIS',
        'CON'
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the standard abbreviation for your Dexterity score?',
      correctAnswer: 'DEX',
      answers: [
        'CHA',
        'DEX',
        'WIS',
        'CON'
      ],
    },
  ],
  1: [
    {
      question: 'Which of these creatures is famous for transforming into treasure to trick adventurers?',
      correctAnswer: 'Mimic',
      answers: [
        'Bugbear',
        'Mimic',
        'Acid Slime',
        'Werewolf'
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'Which type of damage prevents a troll from regenerating?',
      correctAnswer: 'Fire',
      answers: [
        'Ice',
        'Lightning',
        'Radiant',
        'Fire'
      ],
    }
  ],
  2: [
    {
      question: 'How does a monk gain their powers?',
      correctAnswer: 'Through their own life-force or ki',
      answers: [
        'Through nature',
        'Through a deity',
        'Through their own life-force or ki',
        'Through extensive study'
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'Which is a wizard\'s most important piece of equipment?',
      correctAnswer: 'Spellbook',
      answers: [
        'Wand',
        'Spellbook',
        'Robes and wizard hat',
        'Staff'
      ],
    }
  ],
  3: [
    {
      question: 'There are two main types of dragons, metallic and â€¦',
      correctAnswer: 'Chromatic',
      answers: [
        'Chromatic',
        'Aberrant',
        'Abyssal',
        'Celestial'
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'How do clerics get their spells?',
      correctAnswer: 'Gaining the favor of a deity',
      answers: [
        'Elaborate ritual dances',
        'From scrolls',
        'Gaining the favor of a deity',
        'Spellbooks'
      ],
    }
  ],
  4: [
    {
      question: 'The Barbarian class is known for a unique ability that allows them to inflict extra damage. What is it called?',
      correctAnswer: 'Rage',
      answers: [
        'Fury',
        'Intimidation',
        'Wildstrike',
        'Rage'
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the only way to ensure the death of a lich?',
      correctAnswer: 'Destroy its phylactery',
      answers: [
        'Use a resurrection spell',
        'Engulf it in flames',
        'Remove its head',
        'Destroy its phylactery'
      ],
    }
  ],
  5: [
    {
      question: 'Which wizard is known for creating a variety of spells involving illusory hands and fists?',
      correctAnswer: 'Bigby',
      answers: [
        'Halaster',
        'Harry',
        'Bigby',
        'Mordenkainen'
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'What kind of special breath does a silver dragon have?',
      correctAnswer: 'Cold Breath',
      answers: [
        'Fire Breath',
        'Cold Breath',
        'Acid Spray',
        'Lightning Breath'
      ],
    }
  ],
  6: [
    {
      question: 'Which monster is feared not for the danger to an adventurer\'s life, but rather to their magical equipment?',
      correctAnswer: 'Rust monster',
      answers: [
        'Blue dragon',
        'Hook horror',
        'Rust monster',
        'Arcanaloth'
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'Which is the Arcane Tradition that focuses on modifying matter?',
      correctAnswer: 'Transmutation',
      answers: [
        'Abjuration',
        'Evocation',
        'Enchantment',
        'Transmutation'
      ],
    }
  ],
  7: [
    {
      question: 'Which monster has a large central eye, multiple spellcasting eyestalks and floats above the ground?',
      correctAnswer: 'A beholder',
      answers: [
        'A mind flayer',
        'A bullette',
        'A beholder',
        'An intellect devourer'
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'What is another name for a mind-flayer?',
      correctAnswer: 'Illithid',
      answers: [
        'Illithid',
        'Kuo-toa',
        'Malcanthet',
        'Beholder'
      ],
    }
  ],
  8: [
    {
      question: 'This creature can be identified by their lion head and backwards-facing hands.',
      correctAnswer: 'Rakshasa',
      answers: [
        'Githyanki',
        'Rakshasa',
        'Duergar',
        'Ogre'
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'Which kind of undead is Count Strahd von Zarovich?',
      correctAnswer: 'A vampire',
      answers: [
        'A vampire',
        'A revenant',
        'A mummy lord',
        'A lich'
      ],
    }
  ],
  9: [
    {
      question: 'Who is the god that most orcs worship?',
      correctAnswer: 'Gruumsh',
      answers: [
        'Lolth',
        'Tiamat',
        'Gruumsh',
        'Kurtulmak'
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'Which faction of the Forgotten Realms wants to acquire wealth and power, at any cost?',
      correctAnswer: 'The Zhentarim',
      answers: [
        'The Zhentarim',
        'The Harpers',
        'The Thieves\' Guild',
        'The Assassin\'s Blade'
      ],
    }
  ],

}

export default quiz;